We're now on the patient appointments page
Let's create a new appointment
Clicking new appointment
Selecting a doctor from the dropdown
Choosing the appointment date and time
Adding a note about the visit
Submitting the form
Appointment created successfully
Now viewing the doctor's panel
Here are all scheduled appointments
Updating the appointment status to confirmed
Status updated
Opening admin doctors panel
Viewing list of all doctors
Clicking add new doctor
Entering doctor name and email
Selecting department and room number
Creating the doctor account
Doctor added successfully
Opening departments page
Clicking add new department
Entering department name
Department created successfully
Returning to appointments page
Demo completed