We're now on the patient appointments page. Let's create a new appointment.
Clicking new appointment. Selecting a doctor from the dropdown.
Choosing the appointment date and time. Adding a note about the visit.
Submitting the form. Appointment created successfully.
Now viewing the doctor's panel. Here are all scheduled appointments.
Updating the appointment status to confirmed. Status updated.
Switching to the admin panel. Viewing the list of all doctors.
Adding a new doctor. Entering name and email.
Selecting department and room number. Creating the doctor account.
Now on the departments page. Adding a new department.
Entering the department name. Department created successfully.
Back to the appointments page. Demo complete.