Navigating to patient appointments page
Clicking new appointment button
Selecting a doctor from the dropdown
Entering appointment date and time
Adding a note for the visit
Submitting the appointment form
Appointment created successfully
Navigating to doctor's panel
Viewing scheduled appointments
Updating appointment status to confirmed
Status updated successfully
Opening admin doctors panel
Viewing list of all doctors
Clicking add new doctor
Entering doctor name and email
Selecting department and room number
Creating the doctor account
Doctor added successfully
Opening departments page
Clicking add new department
Entering department name
Department created successfully
Returning to appointments page
Demo completed